I'll now call to order the regular meeting of the MIMC Council Tuesday February 25th.
Public input and unscatholic personal hospital announcement set.
Number three action item claims.
Motion to come.
Question 2.
Number 3 action item claims.
Motion to come.
Question 2.
No.
Number 4.
February 10 minutes.
Question 4.
Motion to come.
Number 3.
No.
Number 5.
Number 25.
Number 16.
You all have a budget.
You all have a budget resolution.
Be sure that you all approve.
And it's when we either move money from fund to fund or to general fund to an international
area.
That's not budget.
Or we get unbudget revenue.
Such as on this agenda for all of this amendment.
The library is meeting two grants and some state aid funding.
So that's a new money.
And they're asking to receive it.
It's right in the newspaper.
And the sports is going to be managing the barbeque.
So we're moving that money from words that are at CDV, which is from 302.
A little bit of a digital fund.
Just a little bit.
No.
Second.
Barnes.
Aye.
Joe.
Line six.
Thank you, Joe.
Agreement with the White Enterprise is warehouse evangelism for a community card to be
located at 21L and 207L something.
Sir.
Yes.
What is this?
We've been through by a utilizing of our bank philosophy.
Produced.
Show these locks.
Why use that on.
On each lock.
You'll know.
Yeah.
We can take care of those.
Motion.
Second.
Thank you, sir.
Action number seven.
Green with vision where services to expand services to the level.
We've been on the 13,7777777 since.
You're ready, Gates.
We're working on the vision.
So, we're working on the vision.
Thank you, Scott.
Okay.
Master service.
We went out.
So, this is just for that we already did on the advisory.
This is for the city side.
So, I don't see the other.
It's out.
Motion to approve.
Sorry.
I'll second.
So, fine.
So, on.
On.
the corner of east of Ian 5th Street southeast, make the intersection of 2X stop.
This is Alfa Bass, motion duper.
Second, one, five, two, five, east.
Five.
Hi, number 10, ordinance 25-02, the Mending Exhibit of Section 9-41,
and I'm not going to read that whole thing.
I'm going to do two things, section 9, that's where we won the last tosses.
You can see those rates have a DnR fire district from $65.
Neither of these, so it's okay to 85 DnR fester.
Just kidding.
No, just kidding.
Miss Dsay.
I was, I was paying that, that was kind of black.
It was like, uh...
Motion to prove.
Oh second.
Thank you, Chris.
Thank you, guys, for all you do appreciate it.
Absolutely.
All right, line 11.
Contract with Brandon Davis for the Robs66 Heritage Fest.
Oh, and the amount of 5,600.
So if he's bad, it's the matter of fault.
I don't think she's good or something.
I'll take him for a second.
Is that how I'm going to do that?
Laura, can you kind of go through like the, you know how you said he's opening for
the night that schedule it both days?
Actually, he just had a concert.
Yes, dirty.
It's in Tulsa.
And this is the first year that we've ever had it done.
This is Clash the Band.
Clash the Band.
That's amazing.
Usually it's an April or May before we even get this far.
So I'll make a motion to prove.
We'll go to the business.
May I have a motion on the floor?
We'll go to the second floor.
I'll second floor.
So cool.
Hi.
Bars.
Jones.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
I'll contract with Zach Henry.
We're here at its fastest in a $400.
Motion to a group.
Hi.
Jones.
He's step.
Hi.
We're 13 contract with back to a country for the South 66.
Henry's best with a amount of $500.
Motion to a group.
So cool.
Hi.
Bars.
Jones.
Hi.
He's step.
We're 14 contracts with Evan Honer for the South 66 Heritage Festival in the amount of 25,000
contingent upon submission of required documents.
The contract not been finished.
What's the required documents?
The actual way the required documents were.
I think when that was submitted, it was the insurance in the deadline that we
now have those.
So all of the documents are in place.
And they're good.
And they are good.
Yeah.
Motion to a group.
Hi.
Jones.
This is five.
Each step.
All right.
For 15 contract with John Wolfe with the Route 66 Heritage Festival in the
$10,000.
A contingent upon submission of required documents.
For about $11,000.
I'm going to go ahead.
I have a yesterday.
Yeah.
The W9 is not attached to this.
But I know that I have it in the office.
Yep.
We have it all.
Yes.
Motion to approve.
Say it.
Jones.
Hi.
Go ahead.
On the side.
He's step.
Hi.
Number 16.
Contract.
Can you rate a Horton for the Route 66 Heritage Festival in the amount of
$3,000.
Contended upon submission of required documents.
Thank you at all.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Motion to approve.
I'll second.
Or.
Hi.
Jones.
Circle.
I
Number 17 contract with Tyne Aviel for Rassie's sixth heritage festival in the amount of 22,000 and I
An $0.45 a lot of since
I'm about to go on a
Same staff stuff
Same stage stage stage
And I think that word was just a little bit true
Same spot
So
Yeah, I believe so right now by
This theater
Yeah, yeah, the other questions
Motion to present
Tyne
Hard
Joads
Alright
Then you go
Number 18
Grant
Agreement with the Oklahoma Route 66 Association for a neon sign for the Lila Public Library
Dying grants a little beginning of the street
Nation or association is going to pay them
18% directly
Had a little week
This actual neon or is it
Yes, it had to be a certain percentage of neon
Or maybe it's going to be
We're like no one
This is where the train
New Orleans
Cool
So it's going to happen
I make a motion to approve
Second
Joads
Hi
We'll be able to turn it off on the Route 66 Fest
Because people complained about the lights
The street lights
We'll do the street lights
All right
Number 19
Contract with the Oklahoma Department
Libraries for a grant allowing Alexandria
Speech
To attend the Oklahoma Library Association
Conference in March 25
Public Library
So
Alexandra has our youth library
And she's moving to librarianship
And so she was given the opportunity
Through the moment of our new librarians
To attend the Oklahoma Library Association
I want to thank the street department again for a fantastic job for the streets.
On the big snowstorm, I appreciate all the city workers that still might have to work and sorry, missedy couldn't, but she had a long way to go and all the bad deal.
We don't control their street department, we know.
I always have to warn on the side of certain city officials in my city.
At least you made it on the phone conference with it.
Yeah, it was good.
And that went real well too.
The town hall meeting went real well and it was very well.
Great job everybody.
Thank you.
I wanted to thank everybody for all your help at the senior dance.
That was kind of fun.
Found out that we actually made money.
It was a hit.
Yes, it was a hit.
It wasn't a loss.
Yeah, no.
I'm very impressed.
Thank you to the library.
Library came in today.
I've been offered lots of services and calendar helped with creating an agenda with the senior home.
Very, very, very thankful for that.
I think anybody has events coming up that they want on the calendar.
Please, please reach out to Cali.
Get a log in and do it ourselves.
Do whatever we need to do to get a unified calendar within the city.
There's so much going on right now that if we could get better organized.
I think that will really help our citizens.
I spoke to the United Way a little bit ago to found out the dollar amount.
The senior center was granted $8,500 through the United Way.
It's very exciting.
Very, very exciting.
They would also like to be on that calendar as well.
So what do them about that?
So she'll be reaching out.
That's.
I would like to speaking of events.
Would like to call attention to our line a little theater.
I go to, I try to go to all their place.
They're amazing.
These guys worked super hard to do a wonderful job.
And I just want to call attention to you guys.
I challenge each one of the board members here to take out of these plays and be entertained.
Because it's truly enjoyable.
It's always a good talk.
Challenge accepted.
Can't want to invite me.
Don't challenge.
Just ask me.
We're invited.
Thank you.
And also, you might check out being coming in member of the Colman, which gets you a couple
of tickets for free.
All right.
See the manager communications.
I just want to, like, echo what everyone said on the, you know, cleaning up the town
on, as far as it's never moving on everything I mean.
We did it.
And thank you guys all for cleaning up downtown for the town hall.
I mean, I just checked.
This is what's created in me with the power of social media.
We have 17,000, 600 views on our town hall, which is really wild.
Yeah.
I'm happy to see people care.
So we're getting the word out.
You know, I keep pushing, and I mean, it's like it's good.
So that was cool.
That's all I have.
So I'm 24 a German motion approved.
Second.
Yeah.
We're going to.
Second.
First.